I want to see
أريد أن أرى
who's bullying my sister.
من الذي يتنمر على أختي؟
You are Li Shujing's brother?
أنت أخو لي شوجينغ؟
I had no idea she had a brother.
لم أكن أعلم أن لديها أخاً.
Well, now you do.
حسناً، أنت تعرف الآن.
My name is Liang Yusheng.
اسمي ليانغ يوشنغ.
Give that project back to my sister.
أعد ذلك المشروع إلى أختي.
Consider it
فكر في الأمر
a favor I owe you.
خدمة أدين بها لك.
Kid,
طفل،
how much do you think your favor is worth?
كم تعتقد أن قيمة معروفك؟
What do you mean, kid? That sounds awful.
ماذا تقصد يا فتى؟ هذا يبدو فظيعاً.
Are you helping or not?
هل أنت تساعد أم لا؟
As for me,
أما أنا،
I only help friends.
أنا لا أساعد إلا الأصدقاء.
If you can drink with me until I am satisfied,
إذا استطعت أن تشرب معي حتى أشبع،
I'll treat you as a friend.
سأعاملك كصديق.
(Mijing Club)
(نادي ميجينغ)
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
You can hold your liquor better than your sister.
يمكنك تحمل الكحول بشكل أفضل من أختك.
Do not call me kid.
لا تناديني طفلاً.
Do not speak badly about my sister.
لا تتحدث بسوء عن أختي.
Why are you still so worked up?
لماذا ما زلت متوتراً للغاية؟
Come on, let us go somewhere else.
هيا بنا، لنذهب إلى مكان آخر.
=Secret By My Name=
=سر باسمي=
(Adapted from the novel Hotpot Loves Tangyuan by Ye Yijian)
(مقتبس من رواية "هوت بوت يعشق تانغ يوان" للكاتبة يي ييجيان)
=Episode 6=
=الحلقة 6=
Shujing.
شوجينغ.
That woman...
تلك المرأة...
You're back.
لقد عدت.
Yeah.
نعم.
Where did you go last night?
أين ذهبت الليلة الماضية؟
Nowhere.
لا مكان.
The problem with Lin Xi might be settled.
ربما تم حل مشكلة لين شي .
What?
ماذا؟
The problem with Lin Xi
مشكلة لين شي
might be resolved.
قد يتم حل المشكلة.
Tan Jianfei turned out to be decent enough.
تبين أن تان جيانفي شخص جيد بما فيه الكفاية.
He handled this fairly properly.
لقد تعامل مع هذا الأمر بشكل صحيح إلى حد كبير.
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
What does this have to do with Tan Jianfei?
ما علاقة هذا بتان جيانفي؟
It was me.
كنت أنا.
You dealt with Lin Xi?
هل تعاملت مع لين شي؟
Yes... I did.
نعم... فعلت ذلك.
What?
ماذا؟
What is this?
ما هذا؟
This is nothing.
هذا لا شيء.
Yusheng!
يوشينغ!
You did not use that kind of method, did you?
لم تستخدم هذا النوع من الأساليب، أليس كذلك؟
What kind of method?
أي نوع من الأساليب؟
I won't take advantage of you for nothing.
لن أستغلك بلا مقابل.
The project is yours.
المشروع ملكك.
I'm off.
أنا ذاهب.
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
What?
ماذا؟
Do you want me to take responsibility?
هل تريدني أن أتحمل المسؤولية؟
Kid.
طفل.
I mean,
أعني،
you have to keep your word.
عليك أن تفي بوعدك.
Of course I will.
بالتأكيد سأفعل.
Ms. Li is impressive.
السيدة لي مثيرة للإعجاب.
You managed to take care of Lin Xi.
لقد نجحت في الاعتناء بلين شي.
You were quite impressive last night too.
لقد كنتَ مثيراً للإعجاب للغاية الليلة الماضية أيضاً.
There are so many people around.
يوجد الكثير من الناس حولنا.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
Since Lin Xi is gone,
منذ رحيل لين شي،
let's hand over the Autumn Winter Alpine project
لنسلم مشروع جبال الألب الخريفية الشتوية
to Ms. Li Shujing.
للسيدة لي شوجينغ.
Miss Li,
ميس لي،
can you handle it independently?
هل يمكنك التعامل مع الأمر بشكل مستقل؟
Mr. Zheng, what do you consider independent?
سيد تشنغ، ما الذي تعتبره مستقلاً؟
Like your department,
مثل قسمكم،
independently creating a three-hundred-million financial hole?
هل تسبب ذلك بشكل مستقل في حدوث فجوة مالية بقيمة ثلاثمائة مليون؟
Or like me,
أو مثلي،
turning that hole into leverage to acquire a competitor?
تحويل تلك الثغرة إلى نقطة قوة للاستحواذ على منافس؟
You!
أنت!
Enough.
كافٍ.
Ms. Li can do it.
السيدة لي تستطيع فعل ذلك.
I have faith in her.
أنا أثق بها.
Is there something going on between Shujing and Jianfei?
هل هناك علاقة ما بين شوجينغ وجيانفي؟
Ms. Li might have been with Mr. Tan last night...
ربما كانت السيدة لي برفقة السيد تان الليلة الماضية...
Say it.
قلها.
Miss Li's earring
قرط الآنسة لي
was left last night
تم تركه الليلة الماضية
in the corner of Mr. Tan's bedroom.
في زاوية غرفة نوم السيد تان.
It was turned in by housekeeping this morning.
تم تسليمها من قبل قسم التدبير المنزلي هذا الصباح.
They were together all night.
لقد قضوا الليل معاً.
Do you think it is possible
هل تعتقد أن ذلك ممكن؟
they were discussing the Autumn Winter Alpine
كانوا يناقشون ملابس جبال الألب لخريف وشتاء
embroidery stitching?
غرز التطريز؟
Probably. Yes, probably.
ربما. نعم، ربما.
Probably?
من المحتمل؟
Probably.
من المحتمل.
Get lost!
اغرب عن وجهي!
Ms. Li's waist-shaping cut
قصة السيدة لي التي تُبرز خصرها
is still as sharp as ever.
لا يزال حادًا كما كان دائمًا.
However,
لكن،
the curve seems to be off by
يبدو أن المنحنى غير دقيق.
half a millimeter more than before.
نصف مليمتر أكثر من ذي قبل.
Then perhaps
إذن ربما
you should switch tailors.
يجب عليك تغيير الخياط.
After all, for someone who can't button a shirt
في النهاية، بالنسبة لشخص لا يستطيع إغلاق أزرار قميصه
to misjudge measurements
سوء تقدير القياسات
is hardly surprising.
ليس هذا بالأمر المفاجئ.
Then there is no one more suitable than you.
إذن، لا يوجد أحد أنسب منك.
After all, there is no one else in this world
في النهاية، لا يوجد أحد آخر في هذا العالم
who understands me better.
من يفهمني بشكل أفضل؟
We are at the office.
نحن في المكتب.
Step back.
تراجع للخلف.
Mr. Tan, you seem to have plenty of free time lately.
سيد تان، يبدو أن لديك الكثير من وقت الفراغ مؤخراً.
Dropping by to tell your sister-in-law how to do her job.
زيارة خاطفة لإخبار زوجة أخيك بكيفية القيام بعملها.
Zuoyan, that is a bit premature.
زويان، هذا سابق لأوانه بعض الشيء.
The wedding date isn't set yet.
لم يتم تحديد موعد الزفاف بعد.
No one knows
لا أحد يعلم
what will happen.
ماذا سيحدث؟
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
I came today
لقد أتيت اليوم
to discuss the wedding date
لمناقشة موعد الزفاف
with Shujing.
مع شوجينغ.
Shujing,
شوجينغ،
how about next month?
ماذا عن الشهر القادم؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
We'll discuss personal matters in private.
سنتناقش في الأمور الشخصية على انفراد.
This is the office.
هذا هو المكتب.
That is my Ms. Li,
هذه هي السيدة لي خاصتي،
always so devoted to work.
لطالما كان متفانياً في عمله.
Zuoyan,
زويان،
perhaps you should not stay here,
ربما لا ينبغي لك البقاء هنا،
interrupting us while we discuss work details.
مقاطعيننا أثناء مناقشتنا لتفاصيل العمل.
Shujing,
شوجينغ،
come with me somewhere.
تعال معي إلى مكان ما.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
That's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
Button up.
زرر.
Does this piano's
هل هذا البيانو
soundboard crack
صوت تشقق لوحة الصوت
remind you of the sound
يذكرك بالصوت
of your dad's throat cracking when he died?
هل سمعت صوت طقطقة حلق والدك عندما مات؟
Talk!
يتحدث!
Where did you hide it?
أين أخفيته؟
Hide what?
إخفاء ماذا؟
In B flat.
في سلم سي بيمول.
Li
الذي - التي
put everything he had
وضع كل ما يملك
on the seventh note.
على النوتة السابعة.
You monster!
يا لك من وحش!
Let go of my mom!
دع أمي تذهب!
Monster?
وحش؟
When your dad knelt and begged me,
عندما ركع والدك وتوسل إليّ،
he was far more obedient than that.
كان أكثر طاعة من ذلك بكثير.
Your habit of rummaging through old houses
عادة البحث في المنازل القديمة
is far more honest than the way you talk business.
إنها أكثر صدقاً بكثير من الطريقة التي تتحدث بها عن الأعمال.
The Li family's debt,
ديون عائلة لي،
the Tan family's blood,
دماء عائلة تان،
and that thin,
وذلك الرقيق،
unspoken game
لعبة غير معلنة
of using each other between you and me
استخدام كل منا للآخر بيني وبينك
are almost being erased by Tan Jianfei.
يكاد يتم محوها بواسطة تان جيانفي.
Have you forgotten
هل نسيت؟
how to carve hatred into your bones?
كيف تغرس الكراهية في عظامك؟
That's something I never needed to be taught.
هذا شيء لم أكن بحاجة إلى أن أتعلمه أبداً.
Unlike the Tan family.
على عكس عائلة تان.
You actually check the family records
أنت في الواقع تتحقق من سجلات العائلة
before you start crying at the funeral.
قبل أن تبدأ بالبكاء في الجنازة.
♪A lone bird flying against the crowd♪
♪طائر وحيد يحلق عكس اتجاه الحشد♪
♪Shaking off the dust, yet still circling back♪
♪ينفض الغبار، لكنه لا يزال يعود أدراجه♪
♪Following time's hidden veins toward the next dawn♪
♪نتبع عروق الزمن الخفية نحو الفجر التالي♪
♪Besieged by the night sealed deep below♪
♪محاصرون بالليل، مختومون في الأعماق♪
♪As the mist clears, searching for light's cure♪
♪مع انقشاع الضباب، بحثًا عن علاج النور♪
♪The road is narrow, yet the way I came is not forgotten♪
♪الطريق ضيق، لكن الطريق الذي أتيت منه لم يُنسَ♪
♪An ending that can never be undone♪
♪نهاية لا يمكن التراجع عنها♪
♪Disrupting the old rhythm, laying traps♪
♪إفساد الإيقاع القديم، ونصب الفخاخ♪
♪A board full of snares♪
♪لوح مليء بالطبول♪
♪Carving the past into every smile and word♪
♪ننقش الماضي في كل ابتسامة وكلمة♪
♪After falling, still searching for♪
♪بعد السقوط، ما زلت أبحث♪
♪The old marks♪
♪العلامات القديمة♪
♪Pages filled with attempts to hide the past♪
♪صفحات مليئة بمحاولات إخفاء الماضي♪
♪The next page♪
♪الصفحة التالية♪
♪Is turned, revealing this land of right and wrong♪
♪تتحول، كاشفةً عن هذه الأرض التي فيها الحق والباطل♪
♪A lone bird flying against the crowd♪
♪طائر وحيد يحلق عكس اتجاه الحشد♪
♪Shaking off the dust, yet still circling back♪
♪ينفض الغبار، لكنه لا يزال يعود أدراجه♪
♪Following time's hidden veins toward the next dawn♪
♪نتبع عروق الزمن الخفية نحو الفجر التالي♪
♪Besieged by the night sealed deep below♪
♪محاصرون بالليل، مختومون في الأعماق♪
♪As the mist clears, searching for light's cure♪
♪مع انقشاع الضباب، بحثًا عن علاج النور♪
♪The road is narrow, yet the way I came is not forgotten♪
♪الطريق ضيق، لكن الطريق الذي أتيت منه لم يُنسَ♪
♪The way I came♪
♪الطريقة التي أتيت بها♪